ageofconan.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy policy | Age of Conan | Funcom

Funcom takes the privacy of its customers seriously and wants you to understand how and why it collects, uses and maintains the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use for the Services offered by Funcom.

**What information does Funcom collect?**

Personal Information: Funcom collects information you voluntarily provide during the registration process in order to grant you access to products and service provided by Funcom and its affiliates. This "Personal Information" includes your name, Social application user ID, age, date of birth, sex, zip code, city, state and country and encrypted social application email. Funcom uses this information to to provide access to our products and services.

For paid services it is necessary to collect your name, address and payment information. This information will be provided to a payment service provider and or bank for verification and payment processing.

Computer Information: Funcom may collect and store your internet protocol address. As noted in the Funcom End User License Agreement ("EULA") or Terms of Service agreement ("TOS"), we may use this information to remotely check your computer to determine if any "Restricted Software" (as such term is defined in the EULA or TOS) is installed or if any necessary software patches supplied by Funcom have been installed.

Chat Room Information: Funcom may monitor any Chat room on the Funcom website(s) for the purpose of determining whether a violation of the Chat room guidelines has occurred and to take appropriate action as we deem reasonably necessary. Funcom encourages you not to use your real name or disclose personal information in a Chat room - once posted any personal information will no longer be private.

Non-personal Information: Funcom may from time to time collect information such as number of players on-line for a particular time period, number of players by country, and average session length on an aggregated basis. This non-personal information does not specifically identify you or any other single user.

**How do we protect your personal information and do we share it with others?**

Information In Transit: To protect private and confidential information from interception and visibility to unauthorized persons while in transit, the connection between your web browser and the registration server operated by Funcom is encrypted and verified using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. When setting up a unique session between you and Funcom, the server at Funcom will send its public key to your browser. In return, your browser will generate a randomly generated secret key based on the key it received from Funcom. This key is then sent back and checked by the server at Funcom.

Information In Storage: Information you provide to Funcom is stored on servers operated by Funcom AS, Oslo, Norway and physically placed in North America. The servers handling registrations are placed in a physically shielded environment. By clicking on the padlock symbol in your browser you can check the information encapsulated in the certificate to verify you are connected to the registration server owned and operated by Funcom.

While Funcom uses reasonable efforts to protect your privacy, due to the nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee that a third party will not be able to unlawfully intercept a private communication.

**With whom do you share my information?**

We may provide your personal information on a confidential basis to affiliates of Funcom and third parties necessary to allow Funcom to provide you with the Services.

We may also disclose your personal information to the extent required to cooperate with law enforcement or governmental requests or investigations or pursuant to third party subpoenas or court orders.

**What happens to my information if I terminate the Service?**

Funcom may, but is not obligated to retain your personal information following termination for the purpose of maintaining records, securing payment and complying with legal requirements. Any information retained by Funcom will be maintained by Funcom on the terms set forth above.

**What Other Uses may you make of my personal information? Can I opt-out of information uses and how?**

From time to time Funcom may contact you regarding new games or services available from Funcom or its affiliates ("New Games"). If you do not wish to receive information about new games from Funcom you may elect to "opt-out" or "unsubscribe" in the email you receive and within a reasonable time thereafter Funcom will not notify you regarding New Games.

**What about children?**

Funcom software is not intended for persons under the age of 13. Persons younger than 13 are not authorized to become users of the Funcom Service and Funcom does not knowingly collect personal information from any person under the age of 13.

**What choices do I have about Funcom's use of information about me?**

You can opt-out of receiving information regarding New Games as set forth above.

You may terminate your account with Funcom in which event Funcom may retain your personal information as set forth above.

**Do you sell my information to third parties?**

Funcom does not sell your information to third parties.

**What if you change the Policy?**

In the event Funcom decides to change the Privacy Policy you will receive notice, either by e-mail or the Funcom website. You will have the opportunity to terminate if you do not agree to the change.

Funcom Oslo AS,   
Bestumstubben 11   
N-0281 Oslo   
Norway
